[{"answer": "You know, covering this throughout the day, watching the clashes beginning to spread and intensify across the capital, hearing the reports of clashes breaking out elsewhere, angry mobs of supporters of ousted President Mohamed Morsi, even attacking churches, it felt as if one was beginning to see the very edges of Egyptian society fraying.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "What is your take on what is happening here?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "AMON: It's difficult to judge that.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "And the obvious question, Arwa, I guess, is do you believe that journalists including yourself are coming under deliberate attack here or is it simply being caught up in the general mayhem?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well, it's really scary and just heartbreaking to see.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "How bad do you think this is going to get?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Well, it's really an issue of semantics.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Why are the Americans persisting and pretending otherwise?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Well, I think there's a lot more to this story probably than that's -- we really understand at this point.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "What do you make of all this?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "It does seem strange.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "Where is her mother and father to not know that this guy is creepy and she feels creepy about him?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, the same thing that you're saying.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "What do you read into all this?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Well, you know, here's something -- we haven't had a chance to talk for quite awhile.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "I believe you've taken some today as you would every day, is that correct?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Well, look, a lot of the criticism I think, you know -- first of all, you talk to a guy like Montel and he's been ahead of the curve on this, frankly.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "But what is your response to the criticism you've had this week?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Well -- well, I oppose medical marijuana -- I want to really start by saying that there is a lot that I do agree with, with both Sanjay and Montel.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Why are you so opposed to this?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think that there has been difficulty in studying cannabinoids largely because of a confluence of circumstances that -- that were brought up in the special and in other interviews that we've seen on CNN.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "So the classification seems to be completely wrong, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "That can't be right, can it?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "I think that now that we have more doctors and even Dr. Levy agrees, we need to do the research.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Where do you think this is all going to go?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "Well, you know what, frankly, it was sad, Piers, the story that she told.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "What did you make of what happened?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "I think it helped Kathryn Jackson and -- and Michael's children, Piers.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "But in the end, there (ph) was a picture built that helps AEG in the sense of Jackson's clear long-time use of propofol and all these doctors -- not just Conrad Murray queuing up to supply it for him?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Well, but that's not what I think happened.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "If he was just using Conrad Murray as he had many other doctors to give him what he wanted, does that not in a way help AEG's case, too?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "That's what I think.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "So right now, dollar-for-dollar, Tom, your money would be on AEG losing this case?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "Well, I think what's so shocking about it, if -- if this is, in fact, Hannah who's speaking to the public.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "But what do you think about that, and the -- the fact that she's revealing all this information?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "It's -- it's definitely odd but at the same time I think that...", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Right, I mean, Alyona, it does seem a little odd, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Alyona, when we look at Bradley Manning and Edward Snowden and all these whistleblowers in various ways, are they heroes to you?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "It's not our job to weigh in on that.", "docId": "130814pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "Now, finally, one word, hero or villain, Bradley Manning?", "qSentId": 550}]